hey y'all check it out the audiobook has
finally been released just go to fool's
errand dot u.s. that's the shortcut
it'll take you over to the Amazon page
and very soon actually I got a brand new
website going up at Scott worden org and
so soon you'll be able to buy that
audiobook directly from me but for now
you can still get it at audible and at
amazon.com the audiobook up fools air
and time to end the war in Afghanistan
and yes it's read by me and I'm sorry it
took so long I Nick picked the hell out
of it trying to get it ready for you
guys and then plus it took them forever
after I submitted it to finally release
it but anyway there you go fool's errand
u.s. amazon.com just search for my name
Scott Horton fool's errand and the
audiobook is up there for you also of
course available in paperback and kindle
if you want the eleven hundred and fifty
footnotes wall is the improvement of
investment climates by other means
clouds of its for dummies
[Music]
the Scott Horton show taking out Saddam
Hussein turned out to be a pretty good
deal they hate our freedoms we're
dealing with Hitler revisited we
couldn't wait for that cold war to be
over quickly so we can go and play with
that toys in the sand go and play with
our toys in the sand
no nation could preserve freedom in the
myths of continual warfare
today I authorized the Armed Forces of
the United States in military action in
Libya that action has now begun when the
president desert that means that it is
not only aren't you guys introducing
John Kiriakou he's the host of a show
called loud and clear on Sputnik and
he's the author of the book The
Reluctant Spy about his time in the CIA
he famously went to prison for blowing
the whistle on some CIA torturers the
only CIA man to go to prison regarding
the torture program in any way the
whistleblower and then he also
co-authored a book with Joseph Hickman
the great whistleblower from Guantanamo
Bay who witnessed the murders are not
witnessed the murders but witness the
aftermath of the murders of three men
there in 2006 and that's called the
convenient terrorists all about Abu
Zubaydah welcome back to the show how
are you doing John thanks I'm doing well
thanks thanks for having me good deal
happy to have you here so listen there's
some controversy going on let's start
off with them is well Gina Haspel of
course is the nominee Trump's nominee to
replace Pompeo for CIA director and
you've been saying that in various media
various articles you've written
including in the Washington Post that at
the time you and your friends at CIA
back then called her bloody Gina for her
role in the torture program and I
thought it was really funny actually the
way the guy at NPR News gave you the
third degree over a statement that you
actually retracted although it's pretty
clear what his agenda was oh yeah and
the way that he handled that interview
is amazing to see not really its NPR but
still they're supposed to be the
Liberals you know but instead Sean
Hannity oh yeah oh yeah you know what
the issue is with NPR is that there neo
liberals just like the Hillary Clinton's
just like all these other mainstream
pro-war Democrats they're they're all in
the same boat
I'll tell you the truth I was surprised
that he attacked my integrity I wasn't
surprised that he attacked me but I
decided to just give it right back to
him
I'm glad I did yeah well now and he had
you getting it wrong and and you
conceded it he read the words to you say
here that she videotaped the torture of
Abu Zubaydah you wrote that in our
article for reader supported news a year
ago so what happened with that
yeah you know this was an opinion piece
that I had done for reader supported
news and I had pulled the information
from the front page of the Washington
Post and that's what I used what was on
the Washington Post what everybody else
was reporting because I have to put
everything I write through the CIA's
publications Review Board and so if I'm
offering up something new something
that's never been reported before they
reject that and I didn't want to have it
rejected and so I used what was publicly
available so at the time that you made
that error you were going off of other
reporting but then people are citing you
because hey you're John Kiriakou you're
the guy who knows so then you become the
primary source that people are quoting
but then so you're saying now that that
is wrong yeah she she got there just
after the torture of Abu Zubaydah and
she oversaw the torture of absurdity
Monisha t so this brings up two points
Scott number one does it really matter
which one she tortured I mean is it
better to have tortured one than the
other or we should be forgiving of her
torturing one and not the other well
it's a almost sort of kinda a little bit
I mean the first thing is just because
the ProPublica story came out and was
cited by Rand Paul and others that was
they were partially citing you and they
were partially citing others that she
was in charge of torturing zubeida so
for the retraction it just it was a huge
story that had to be retracted
regardless of the fact that well yeah
but she tortured in a shiri instead and
I guess there is a difference right
because Anna shiri was actually guilty
of I don't know if he was in on the 9/11
plot I think he was in on the 9/11 plot
but he was certainly a real al Qaeda guy
as opposed to Abu Zubaydah who was
mostly just some schmuck right then you
wrote the book on him not
not necessarily Joe and I in the book we
say that Abu Zubaydah was was not the
mastermind the terrorist mastermind that
the White House and the CIA said he was
but he was certainly a bad guy he was
the commander of Al Qaeda's two training
camps in southern Afghanistan he was the
the founder of Al Qaeda's safe house and
to shower the house of martyrs he was
the guy that that issued the paychecks
and and made the fake passports and got
you a ticket home if you were done with
the fight so he was a bad guy and my
second point though is is about ray
Bonner the arter the author of that
article first of all I don't think the
article should have been retracted I
think it should have been corrected
because it was just that one sentence it
should have been corrected but Ray
Bonner here's this guy former New York
Times journalist the the author of the
article for ProPublica does this guy not
do any research like the any research at
all does he have no national security
sources that he can that he can call on
he has to rely on John kiriakos op-ed in
reader supported news well I mean it
certainly was a fair point that you made
on NPR that he should have called you he
should rather than just you know writing
based on that you're pretty easy to get
ahold of yeah I am but now it's so
zubeida and I haven't read the book
because man there's a lot of books I
haven't read that I should have read but
I'm getting a lot of mixed signals about
Abu Zubaydah I mean I've heard him
certainly describe more or less as like
a travel agent the kind of guy who
brought the al-qaeda guys wives to come
and visit for a while and this kind of
thing Ransome camps but well and I don't
know if this is true either because this
reporter's work has come into question
from time to time as well but Ron
Suskind quotes george w bush telling
george tenant hey i said he was
important you're not gonna make me lose
face on this are you George because Bush
had invoked zubeida over and over and
over again as this is exactly why we
have to torture because we've got our
hands on guys like zubeida who was the
number three commander of al Qaeda and
we had a torture
we'll get to what they tortured out of
him in a minute but we had to torture
all these things out of them and so well
I don't know clarify for me yeah you
know I generally hate Ron Suskind guts
but he's right on that point it was it
was George W Bush that went on national
television and said that Abu Zubaydah
was the number three in al-qaeda and
ordered the CIA to catch him now the
work that Joe Hickman did in our book
the book we brought together really it's
it's more Joe's research than it is mine
I just sort of recounted my personal
experience in it but Joe did this
groundbreaking research in which he
found that there were two Abu Zubaydah's
there was the Abu Zubaydah we captured
and there was his first cousin also
named Abu Zubaydah not unusual in the
Middle East well when you look at the
two files mixed into one not realizing
that it's two different guys you say oh
my god disguise the terrorist mastermind
he's he's a terrorist Superman like how
can he be in all these different places
at the same time well he couldn't it's
because there were two of them so if you
put them together sure this is a very
bad guy we've got to stop this guy if
you realize there are two different guys
you know it's bad but it's not that bad
and he certainly wasn't the number three
in al-qaeda and which by the way I'm not
trying to say you know this guy in a
Syria if he was involved in September
11th deserve to be tortured but it
sounds like if zubeida wasn't he
definitely did not deserve to be
tortured he did not he did not deserve
it no she was not in on 9/11 but he was
the alleged mastermind of the Cole
bombing so also a very bad guy but you
know back to the point that I made the
first time I was on your show if these
guys are as bad as we say they are then
why don't we charge them with a crime
and put them on trial and we've never
done that No
well with the USS Cole they have
prosecuted some of those guys and then
but torch you know rendition and
tortured the rest is how did that break
down yeah well they went after the
people that they believed to be the
masterminds of all these different
attacks
and and they were successful in just
about every instance of either capturing
or killing them and when they captured
them in that period between 2002 and
2005 they immediately sent him to a
secret location then they started the
the so-called enhanced interrogation
techniques they extracted these
confessions or what they believe to be
confessions and then that was the end of
it because then when they were turned
over to military authorities or to the
Judge Advocate General's office at
Guantanamo they were told we can't use
any of this information because it was
extracted during torture it was though
it was as though at the Justice
Department in 2001 and 2002 the
righthand didn't know what the left hand
was doing on the one hand you had the
Office of Special Counsel telling the
CIA sure you can go ahead and torture
these guys it's legal because we say so
in this one instance and then on the
other hand you have the US Attorneys
offices saying wait a minute wait a
minute we can't prosecute these guys
because they were tortured and torture
is illegal so now they're in this limbo
situation look at Abu Zubaydah he's been
he's been in our custody now for 16
years and he's never been charged with a
crime oh he's not even one of the ones
being prosecuted because they are
prosecuting Khalid Sheikh Mohammed down
there and they're rinsing then I'll
shoot and they tortured both of those
guys right yeah well they're trying to
and both of those prosecutions have
screeched to a halt just because they
don't know what to do about this torture
the information extracted during torture
which and by the way if people read
Khalid Sheikh Mohammed's confession he
admits that he sank the main and the
Lusitania and went behind convincing FDR
to let the Japanese go ahead and attack
Pearl Harbor because they must
everything I was mocked once in an
interview because I said that at one
point he confessed to kidnapping the
Lindbergh baby what do you do with all
that information yeah I mean I was
joking but that's how serious it is well
and I think he was at that point who
knows but almost it seemed to me like he
was kind of in humor kind of just saying
oh yeah that's right guys
today's the day of my big confession
write all this down and it was almost
like he was sending a message that you
know are you buying this cuz this is
what they've tortured me in to say
hinder sight you know the subtext to me
was like wait this is the guy that put
Castro in power I have in Cuba in the
first place way back when exactly anyway
you know the thing about Khalid Sheikh
Mohammed too is unlike most of these
other guys he realizes that his life is
over that he is never gonna see the
light of day again and so with that
understanding he knows that he has
nothing to lose by just saying anything
that pops into his head and that's what
he does all right so let's talk about
well I want to get back to Gina Haspel
in a minute but what the hell we got a
little bit time so I'm interested in the
Iraq war lies that they tortured out of
Abu Zubaydah and sheikh al Libi
specifically and we already know i think
that they had the egyptians torture al
Libi into saying that saddam had taught
al-qaeda how to make chemical weapons
and hijack airplanes but what exactly
lies do you note that did they torture
out of zubeida
in regards to implicating Saddam Hussein
you know specifically out of Abu
Zubaydah I don't know that was after my
time there but this was also an ongoing
problem that was coming out of the White
House
you'll recall that on September 12 2001
richard perle famously went to the White
House and said we've got to attack Iraq
the Iraqis were behind this now of
course the Iraqis weren't behind it the
Iraqis were never behind it Osama bin
Laden hated Saddam Hussein as much as he
hated us but but pearl and the neo-cons
had an agenda they had an agenda from
the very beginning and what they had as
their trump card was the fact that
Saddam had laid out a plot to kill the
first president Bush during a visit to
Kuwait in 1993 and so so they
capitalized on that and they used it to
propagandize George W Bush who frankly
didn't know any better and and was
getting was getting competing
information intelligence whether it was
coming from the CIA or from the Pentagon
because the Pentagon had recruited Ahmed
Chalabi after the CIA had issued a Burn
Notice on him forbidding any CIA officer
from coming into contact with him so the
the intelligence was biased and faulty
and propaganda you had a vice president
that you couldn't trust who's pushing
you into war then you have you know
these al-qaeda prisoners who are being
tortured into saying that Iraq had
something to do with the 9/11 attacks
you have fake intelligence saying that
Mohammed Atta had flown to Prague to
meet with the with the station chief of
the Iraqi intelligence service there I
mean sure the the nature of intelligence
is that it's sometimes conflicting but
this was ridiculous this was this was a
concerted effort by an element of
opinion makers in Washington to push us
into a war of choice all right Jill real
quick here's how to support this show
first of all buy my book fool's errand
it's a fool's errand at us and the
audiobook is now available as well sign
up for the show feeds iTunes stitcher
and RSS this that and everything it's
all at Scott Horton org and also you can
subscribe at youtube.com slash Scott
Horton show the full archive 4600
interviews all available for you on
YouTube as well now and then check out
Scott Horton org slash donate for 20
bucks you'll be able to get the
audiobook here very soon from there also
$50 if you want a signed copy of the
book fools air and the paperback $100
you get a QR code SILVER commodity disc
and anyone who donates $200 or more gets
a lifetime subscription to listen and
think libertarian audiobooks take PayPal
one-off and monthly donations take all
different kinds of Bitcoin and digital
currencies especially Zen Cash that Zen
system dot IO but anyway all those
addresses are there at Scott Horton org
slash donate and of course there's
patreon.com there was a problem with it
but the problems fixed now patreon.com
slash Scott Hortons show if you want to
donate per interview that's how to do
that and anybody who donates a
or more on patreon who signs up for $1
more per interview we'll get 2 free
audiobooks from listen and think audio
and that could include my book now too
so there you go find out all about all
that stuff at scott Horton org slash
donate hey thanks for bringing up the
anthrax there because you know right
Dawson pointed out to me what I believe
is the very first instance of that story
and it's in the London Times and it says
right there according to Israeli
intelligence sources they witnessed not
only did Mohamed Atta
meet Iraqi intelligence in Prague they
witnessed the Iraqi intelligence officer
hand Mohamed Atta up one anthrax total
lie that was a total lie and you know I
remember thinking right around the time
that we were crossing the border into
Iraq or in the days immediately
preceding that I remember thinking I
wonder if this is all a giant Israeli
deception and denial program if it is
man this is classic because they're
pushing us right into a war we really
didn't want to fight that's almost
exactly the title Bush's Cincinnati
speech denial and deception hey as long
as we're talking about it
Julian Borgia wrote in The Guardian 1
called the spies who pushed for war and
Robert Dreyfus has one in the nation
called agents of influence and Bamford
writes about it in his book a pre axed
for war that yeah the Israelis were
manufacturing fake intelligence and
stovepiping it right into the stream
there in order to push this thing
Lawrence Wilkerson has said on this show
that out of all the neocons and they're
all a bunch of his reversers but he
thought that David Wormser and Douglas
Feith were both working outright as
agents on behalf of the Israeli
government I would not be surprised by
that and it's something that probably
deserved an investigation back then yeah
I wouldn't be surprised well I can think
of a few there were there were
independent there were journalists
investigations but yeah that was about
it
now ok so
do you know about where any of these
guys tortured into implicating Iraq
other than zubeida and Libby not that I
know of and Libby was the big one
Libby was the one that they you know
specifically set out to get him to say
that it was Iraq hmm and now all the
orange alerts you know there's a story I
guess I know Marcy wheelers written
about this and I guess it was in the
torture the Senate torture report that
at one point colleagues Sheikh Mohammed
said yeah I have some Nation of Islam
guys running around plotting to blow up
Montana and they sent a bunch of CIA run
it to go run around to try to find this
Nation of Islam terrorist plot that
Khalid Sheikh Mohammed had made up and I
was just wondering like come on and
these guys when they know that their job
is torturing lies out of these guys to
keep everybody's mom afraid so they can
lie us into war with Iraq don't tell me
they really believed that al Qaeda had
gotten the Nation of Islam to come up
with some plot against know that that's
nonsensical and what they would do in
that case is once Abu Zubaydah says it
they would write it up as an
intelligence report and then they would
put they would put the identical
information in a memo format and send an
official memo to the FBI and then the
FBI would elect to either ignore it or
check it out and my guess is they would
ignore something that ridiculous
well in this story apparently they went
you know all haywire which you know they
got to pretend to be working doing
something I guess true all right okay so
now Gina Haspel I guess tell me
everything that you can tell me about
her you've already said that the
retraction is correct that she arrived
in Thailand after Abu Zubaydah had been
transferred to is it
are they right about this that he went
from there to the torture prison in
Poland that by the way used to be a Nazi
base before it was a Soviet base before
it was an American one well I got to
tell you that I when I when I did the
first op-ed for reader supported news
the one that that was used in that Pro
Publica piece the one I see here ago
yeah for me here ago from February of
two
17 I sent it to the CIA publications
review board and they redacted
everything having to do with Gina
hospitals background except the the
piece that that got out the sentence
that got out saying that she was in
Thailand so I I can't say what she's
done overseas I can't even use the names
of those countries all I can say is it's
been reported widely in the press but I
can't talk about those countries at all
okay so well you were able to say before
that it was correct that in the in the
retraction that she didn't get there
until after he was gone he said that I
said that she got to the secret location
after he was done okay yeah the Thailand
part was mine never I've never used the
word Thailand
and even now just now you didn't okay
no no but so so she was the chief of
staff to Jose Rodriguez yes and so what
exactly was his job again well at the
time Jose was the director of the
counterterrorism center at CIA he
replaced cofre black in March of 2002
and as soon as he became the chief he
pulled Gina Haspel in as his chief of
staff and Jose had been chief of staff
to Co for black before he became
director so these are all very senior
positions we're talking about all right
and so yeah this is the thing now I
forgot which congressman it was who
literally used the phrase but she was
just following orders
oh my god yeah and I'm not sure who I'm
plagiarizing here but it was somebody
and it may have been in one of your
recent articles that you wrote that she
was giving orders yeah she was I mean so
you can't tell me which country she was
traveling in in this and that but can
you explain to what degree she was a
boss coming up with implement you know
coming up with the policies about with
the others and and then to what degree
she's actually in charge of implementing
them sure the policy was was created by
a group of people it was collaborative
in nature so you have
all these senior intelligence service
officers in the counterterrorism center
they're coming up with with these
techniques using the two contracts
psychologist Mitchell and Jessen and
then presenting it to the director and
the general counsel and then it goes
over to the White House for approval
then to the Justice Department then back
to the White House for the president's
signature so that's how the policy was
created once the policies created then
it's up to to those components in CTC to
carry it out so what's the most
sensitive the most important position in
that whole structure it's the chief of
base for the secret site so who does
Jose Rodriguez name he names the person
that he trusts the most
and that was Gina Haspel now there's
been a lot made in the press too about
whether Gina was the chief of the base
the secret site or chief of the station
for the whole country I would posit that
the chief of station probably didn't
even know that this was happening in his
own country
that's how sensitive this operation was
so Gina Haspel was the top dog she was
the one who oversaw everything and
everybody involved Wow so now what do
you make then of Diane Feinstein who
knows all of this I mean listen Diane
Feinstein is nothing but an endless list
of problems and we could start yes
direction but you know she's been pretty
good on torture first Senator John she's
been okay
the problem with Dianne Feinstein though
is that she is a longtime cheerleader
for the CIA and the only time that she
really took exception the only time she
really got angry
was when John Brennan finally confessed
to having ordered his officers to hack
into the Senate intelligence committees
computer system which is an illegal act
of course but was never prosecuted that
was the only time that she's actually
gone under the floor of the Senate and
criticized the CIA now on the torture
program she could have stopped it don't
that when this whole thing was was going
down she was the chairman of the
Intelligence Committee she's the head
overseer and all she had to do was to
say listen I don't care what the Justice
Department says you're not doing this
that's what overseers are for but she
never said any of that she just let it
go forward yeah well and then I mean at
least she did the the investigation
later the same one that you're talking
about where they accidentally gave her
their own report and then and went and
tried to get the FBI to prosecute the
Senate staffers who'd they given it to
for stealing it yeah which is amazing
right they had the nerve it's incredible
that they had the unmitigated gall to
file a crimes report against the Senate
staffers who were preparing the torture
report it was shocking to me hey you
know any of us that the CIA is a
separate co-equal branch of government
at least I mean they certainly weren't
calling her ma'am in that case right
they were calling her Diane you know
that's right that's right
well she she blocked Gina Haspel in 2013
from becoming deputy director of the CIA
for operations d-do she would have
replaced jose rodriguez when he retired
and the reason she did that is because
she said that she had questions about
Gina's activities at the secret site so
a couple of days ago when Gina's named
director a reporter for Politico asked
Feinstein her thoughts and she said that
she's gotten to know G in Haspel as
deputy director that they've had dinner
together and she's gonna need to answer
some questions but that Feinstein has
great respect for her well that's
exactly the opposite of what she was
saying in 2013 and the only thing that's
changed is that they've had dinner
together yeah so what kind of oversight
is that yeah not much so Rand Paul's
come out against her yeah but he's not
on the committee you know yeah he'll get
to vote in the in the general thing but
so is anybody on the
cheri Committee liable to put her
through the wringer at all and then it
doesn't matter does it because even her
confirmation hearing will be in secret
right yeah yeah her confirmation hearing
there will be a couple of minutes of
open session where you know the TV
cameras can show show her sitting there
in front of the panel but the hearing
itself the meet of the hearing it's all
going to be in the Senate Intelligence
Committee vault it's a classified
hearing and it'll be closed off so
there's only one member of the committee
that has come out solidly against her
and that's Ron Wyden a Democrat of
Oregon there have been a couple of other
senators Bernie Sanders Elizabeth Warren
Brian Schatz of Hawaii who have said
that that they're opposed and then that
they'll vote no last night Ron Paul or
I'm sorry Rand Paul said that he would
filibuster both Pompeo and Haspel and
that's great but the last time he tried
to filibuster a nominee he only lasted a
day or two so what we need is we need
somebody to bottle it up in committee I
don't think that Wyden has the
wherewithal to do that if you can't
bottle up in committee you're gonna need
a lot of senators to filibuster or
failing that you're gonna need 40 no
votes so that they can't end cloture
well and thank goodness for partisanship
on this you know the Liberals and the
progressives the leftist I'll give them
credit have really stayed good on war
this whole time but but people between
them and Trump have been really silent
on war through the whole years they're
trying to find a way to slink back to
being guests on this stuff and so here's
an opportunity for them to say look
Bushehr a torturer so we can you know
try to you know find a way to oppose so
and this is the thing is and I've heard
you talk about this about you know just
the broader statements about the
corruption of American society at this
point and certainly in the government
where this is even a question where this
could be allowed to happen it's the same
as you know in 2004 that you know yeah
of course John Kerry is just as bad as
George Bush in every way
and even voted for the war but yeah
George Bush lied us into war he has to
be fired
it doesn't matter Jimmy Carter's the one
running against him it doesn't matter
who's running against him he must be
held accountable for lying us into war
and I remember telling that to people
and them going huh it didn't even occur
to them that yet know the thing is is if
you're a guilty war criminal then at the
very least we don't promote you to the
highest level exactly
exactly it's like we've gone nuts and
when I say something but you know I give
a lot of interviews Scott and when I
when I go on these shows and I say
listen we're supposed to be a country of
laws we're supposed to be a country that
respects its constitution people people
write me off as this you know
libertarian fringe weirdo that when when
what I'm saying is is mainstream and
it's exactly what the founding fathers
were saying yeah well and you know this
is the thing to man is about the law is
it was already against the law of
torture people
but what Obama did was he said I have
ordered an end to these programs but he
didn't say in his executive order that I
am ordering the executive branch of
government to once again recognize the
fact that the law bans torture it always
did and you know the anti torture
statutes are still there I mean I think
am I right that George Washington's
orders from the Revolutionary War still
stand you're not allowing this stuff yes
besides that we've got a federal torture
Act where which which specifically
prohibits exactly those techniques that
we used and and we executed Japanese
soldiers for waterboarding American
prisoners of war after after World War
two so the law never changed
yeah Ronald Reagan Justice Department he
and ed Meese prosecuted a Texas sheriff
for waterboarding summer that's right
which and now look they did I mean come
on you know you're a CIA guy so I don't
know if you want to say this or or if
it's for or against interest to
emphasize this but the CIA has been
torturing people since they're created
since before and you know when they were
the OSS I'm sure as well and they are
legendary instructors
torture to torturers in their employ and
right-wing fascist dictatorships all
across this planet so it's not that they
don't torturous just that it's always
been illegal this whole time yeah it has
been I think over the years that's been
that's been the case now that changed
that changed in 1975 and 76 with the
with the Church Committee and the pike
committee on Capitol Hill but after 9/11
we really seriously back slid yeah
all right man well so I'm trying to
think of what questions I'm not asking
about Haspel that you could answer I
know that you're under restrictions as a
former CIA officer yeah yeah I really
can't say any more than that well thanks
again for coming on the show man really
appreciate it thanks my pleasure take
care all right you guys that's John
Kiriakou former CIA officer host loud
and clear on Sputnik he wrote The
Reluctant spy and then he co-authored
with Joseph Hickman a book called the
convenient terrorists all about Abu
Zubaydah and his cousin Abu Zubaydah all
right so you just learned stuff on
skyward you show Scott Horton org
youtube.com slash Scott Horton show
fool's errand us the audiobook is out by
the audiobook fool's errand u.s. and
anti-war calm libertarian Institute org
and follow me on Twitter at Scott Burton
show thanks all right you guys here's
who supports this show first of all the
great Mike Swanson
he wrote this incredible book called the
war state about the rise of the
permanent military-industrial complex
and the new right after World War two
it's a really important history I think
you'll really like it's the worst state
it's on amazon.com and the worst state
calm and also he gives great investment
advice if you have any money to invest
at Wall Street window dot-com Wall
Street window calm for all the financial
news and the great advice for Mike
Swanson and when you follow his advice I
know he recommends that you keep aleast
some of your savings in metals and what
you want to do then is go to Roberts and
Roberts
courage Inc that's our RBI CEO our RBI
CEO and platinum palladium gold and
silver of course as well
they take the slightest Commission and
provide great service and if you buy
with Bitcoin there is no service fee at
all
that's our RBI doubt Co for all your
precious metals and then of course Zen
cash it's a new digital currency but
it's also an encrypted messaging app and
file transfer app and you can learn all
about it at Zen system dot IO that Zen
system dot IO for Zen cash and then
Liberty stickers calm and got a brand
new website in fact just don't even go
to the current website wait like 15
minutes and then go she's got a brand
new website going up there for liberty
stickers calm it'll be up sometime next
week and I finally got illustrator again
so we're gonna be getting some new
stickers up there lots of good anti
government propaganda for you there at
Liberty stickers calm and listen if you
want a new website a 2018 model website
you got to keep up with the times for
your business or whatever it is you're
doing what you do is go to expand
designs comm / Scott and you'll save 500
bucks